http://www.c-comsat.com/privacy-policy

Ka-band DRIVEAWAYS
Ka-75V (ViaSat/Eutelsat)
Ka-75V-KASAT (Eutelsat)
Ka-98G (Avanti)
Ka-98H (Yahsat)
Ka-98V (ViaSat/Eutelsat)
Ka-98H/Jup (Hughes)
Ka-band FLYAWAYS
MP-60-MOT (Motorized ManPack)
MP-80-MOT (Motorized ManPack)
MP-100-MOT (Motorized ManPack)
FLY-75V (ViaSat/Eutelsat)
FLY-98G (Avanti)
FLY-98H (Yahsat)
FLY-98V (ViaSat/Eutelsat)
Ku-band FLYAWAYS
MP-60-MOT (Motorized ManPack)
MP-80-MOT (Motorized ManPack)
MP-100-MOT (Motorized ManPack)
X-band FLYAWAYS
Flyaway Antenna MP-60-MOT (Motorized Ku/Ka/X Band ManPack)
Flyaway Antenna MP-80-MOT (Motorized Ku/Ka/X Band ManPack)
Flyaway Antenna MP-100-MOT (Motorized Ku/Ka/X Band ManPack)
FIXED MOTORIZED ANTENNAS
ALL FMAs
Ku-band FMAs
1.2m (FMA-120)
1.8m (FMA-180)
1.8m (FMA-180+)
2.4m (FMA-240)
C-band FMAs
2.4m (FMA-240)
1.8m (FMA-180)
1.8 (FMA-180+)
Ka-band FMAs
1.2m (FMA-120Ka)
ACCESSORIES
Powersmart (PS 2480)
Beacon Receiver (BR 300L)
Commitment to Privacy
C-COM Satellite Systems Inc. (“we”/”us”) respects the privacy of your information.  This Privacy Policy provides information on how we collect, store and use any personal information received through our website, www.c-comsat.com (the “Website”) and our mobile satellite products and services (the “Services”) available on the terms of the relevant Terms and Conditions applicable to you and this Privacy Policy.
By using the Website and/or the Services, you consent to the use and disclosure of your Personal Information (as defined below) as described in this Privacy Policy.   Subject to the exceptions below, Your Personal Information will not be used for any other purpose or disclosed further without your consent.  You can withdraw your consent at any time but withdrawing consent may result in your inability to continue using the Website and/or the Services.
Important Exception to Consent.  We may disclose your Personal Information to a third party without your consent if we have reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be causing injury to or interference with (either intentionally or unintentionally) our rights or property, other Website users, other users of the Services or anyone else (including the rights or property of anyone else) that could be harmed by such activities.  We may disclose Personal Information when we believe in good faith that such disclosure is required by and in accordance with the law.  We may also be required to disclose Personal Information when your actions violate or appear to violate our Terms and Conditions.
Personal and Non-Personal Information.
“Personal Information” means information about an identifiable individual, such as your name, age, gender, e-mail address, location, telephone number.  “Non-Personal Information” means information that cannot be used to identify a specific individual and includes information of an anonymous nature such as IP addresses when not combined with the personal information of the computer user to which they relate.
Only Personal Information is governed by this Privacy Policy and you agree that we are not subject to any restrictions in respect of our use or disclosure of Non-Personal Information we collect as a result of your use of the Website and/or the Services.
Collection and Use of Information
Our goal is to collect, use and disclose only that information reasonably required to enable us to provide the particular product or service that you have requested, to maintain our customer/visitor lists and or to respond to your inquiries or feedback.  We may also use information received through the Website and the Services to manage your account, to market to you and to advise you about current and future services.   If at any time you decide that you do not want to receive certain communications from us, you can send an email to us (see Contact Us below).
In order to receive the Services, you will be required to open an account by submitting certain information to us.  This information will typically include your name, postal address and contact number.
System Logs.  When accessing the Website, we record information on our system logs from your browser like your IP address, cookies and the pages you’ve requested.  Your IP address is reported by your web browser whenever you visit a page on the Website.  This information, together with other anonymous information is recorded passively and used to gather information regarding the date and time of your visit and products and services you searched and viewed.  Cookies are small files that collect usage data about use of the Website and Services.  We don’t use cookies to collect Personal Information about you.  By going into the options section of your Internet browser, you can instruct your Internet browser to turn off cookies
Disclosures and Transfers
We disclose Personal Information in connection with the following:
– Law & Compliance.  Your Personal Information may be available to the government or government agencies in the countries in which that information is stored and your information may be accessed by those governments or agencies under a lawful order, irrespective of the safeguards we have put in place for the protection of your Personal Information.
– Third Party Services.  From time to time we may employ trusted third parties to help us manage and improve the Website and Services.  Some of the roles they fulfill for us may include hosting, data storage, maintenance of the Website and marketing.  These third parties may have limited access to databases of Website user information solely for the purpose of carrying out their functions and they will be subject to contractual restrictions prohibiting them from using the information about our users for any other purpose.
– Transactional Transfers.  We may also disclose your Personal Information in connection with a corporate re-organization, a merger or amalgamation with another entity, a sale of all or a substantial portion of our assets or stock, provided that the information disclosed continues to be used for the purposes permitted by this Privacy Policy by the entity acquiring the information.  We may also disclose Personal Information in connection with the negotiation of any of the foregoing transactions (including for due diligence activities in respect of such transactions) provided that any such disclosure is done pursuant to a written confidentiality agreement with the entity with whom we may transact.
We may disclose Personal Information in some other limited circumstances, but we will specifically describe them to you when we collect the information, or when required, such as in the terms of use for new service capabilities.
Third Party Sites & Links
The Website may include links to third party websites or service offerings.  We have no control over third party websites and the provision of links in no way constitutes an endorsement, authorization or representation of our connection to that third party.  If you access third party sites using the links on the Website, you should read the privacy policies of those sites and be aware that they may follow different rules regarding the use or disclosure of your Personal Information.
Security
The security of your Personal Information is important to us.  We use commercially reasonable efforts to store and maintain your Personal Information in a secure environment.  We take technical, contractual, administrative, and physical security steps designed to protect Personal Information that you provide to us.  Where there has been a breach of security or confidentiality, we will respond appropriately including making any legally-required disclosures and putting in place measures necessary to restore the integrity of our systems. We also don’t sell customer lists.  Our Website is hosted with GoDaddy Hosting Services.
Amendment of this Policy
We reserve the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time and will post an appropriate notice on the Website.   Any non-material change (such as clarifications) to this Privacy Policy will become effective on the date the change is posted and any material changes will become effective ten (10) days after their posting on the Website.  Once a new Privacy Policy becomes effective, it will apply to all Personal Information submitted by you or collected about you both before and after the date such new Privacy Policy took effect.  The date on which the latest update was made is indicated at the bottom of this document.  We recommend that you print a copy of this Privacy Policy for your reference and revisit this policy from time to time to ensure you are aware of any changes.  Your continued use of the Website and Services signifies your acceptance of any changes.
Access and Accuracy
You have the right to access the Personal Information we hold about you in order to verify the accuracy of that information.  Upon receipt of your written request, we will provide you with a copy of your Personal Information.  We will endeavor to deal with all such requests for access in a timely manner.
Retention
We will keep your Personal Information for as long as necessary for the operation of the Website and Services or as required by law, which may extend beyond the termination of our relationship with you. In general, once you inform us that you no longer wish to use the Website or Services, we will delete your records from our active databases but we may retain an archival copy.
Contact Us
If you have any questions or suggestions regarding our Privacy Policy, please contact us at privacy@c-comsat.com.
Last revised: January 2012
CONTACT US
Interested in learning more or speaking with an expert?
Connect with Us
NEWS RELEASES
C-COM TO PRESENT AT THE BENZINGA GLOBAL SMALL CAP CONFERENCE ON DECEMBER 8TH
December 7, 2020
C-COM TO PRESENT AT THE VIRTUAL FALL INVESTOR SUMMIT ON NOVEMBER 16TH – 18TH
November 12, 2020
© C-COM Satellite Systems Inc, 2020. All rights reserved.
